<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lorelei Labs</title><link>http://example.org/</link><description>Recent content on Lorelei Labs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>It's Definitely Not Nitro!</title><link>http://example.org/blog/dnn/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/blog/dnn/</guid><description>Announcing DNN (Definitely Not Nitro) TL;DR: The developers for Not Quite Nitro have a very misleading privacy policy that admits to their bot, Not Quite Nitro, storing sensitive information about users in the case of internal errors on their end without their knowledge. We did not like their policy or practices, so we decided to make an open-source alternative.
What&amp;rsquo;s the Problem? We have a Discord server where user privacy is sacred.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://example.org/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/projects/</guid><description>Come back soon! We are still writing this page.</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>http://example.org/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/about/</guid><description>Lorelei Labs is a group of volunteer developers who are focused on developing AI software that is sustainable, scalable, and most importantly, truly open for everyone.
We are most well known for our efforts in developing open source dialogue and story telling language models, but we do our own research and development towards the sustainable hosting of these gigantic AI models.</description></item><item><title>Privacy</title><link>http://example.org/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/privacy/</guid><description>Effective: May 7th, 2022
Contact: You can email us at anthony.mercurio@protonmail.com and our mailing address is 8607 West Mariposa Drive Phoenix, AZ 85037 United States.
Access to your Content. We will only access the content that you voluntarily provide to us to provide our Services to your account. Your content will not be viewed by any agent or member of Lorelei Labs without explicit consent from yourself. In order to perform our services, we may need to access, transform, and transmit your content between Lorelei Labs and yourself.</description></item></channel></rss>