<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lorelei Labs</title><link>https://hitomi-team.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Lorelei Labs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hitomi-team.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>An Image is Worth a Thousand Words</title><link>https://hitomi-team.github.io/blog/thousand-words/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hitomi-team.github.io/blog/thousand-words/</guid><description>Zero-Shot Image Captioning Allowing Dialog Language Models to approximate the content of an image through Image Captioning with the help of CLIP. Overview We allowed Language Models like GPT-J 6B to be able to have an approximate overview of images by classifying an image with labels using natural language. Our implementation was heavily inspired through Google Research&amp;rsquo;s Socratic Models which aims to provide multimodal reasoning for Large Language Models such as GPT-3.</description><content>&lt;h2 id="zero-shot-image-captioning">Zero-Shot Image Captioning&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Allowing Dialog Language Models to approximate the content of an image through Image Captioning with the help of CLIP.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="overview">Overview&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We allowed Language Models like GPT-J 6B to be able to have an approximate overview of images by classifying an image with labels using natural language. Our implementation was heavily inspired through Google Research&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href="https://socraticmodels.github.io/">Socratic Models&lt;/a> which aims to provide multimodal reasoning for Large Language Models such as GPT-3.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://i.imgur.com/SxRLMzg.png" alt="Example">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Our Image Captioning system works with multiple categories of labels ranging from fictional characters to what medium the image was created in to what objects are present within the image. With more and more diverse labels to classify an image against, the Image Captioning system would be able to more accurately approximate an image into natural language. It gathers the &lt;code>top-k&lt;/code> labels with the highest probability for all of the label sets when sorted, as erraneous labels would inevitably have the highest probability in some sets.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="use-in-chatbots">Use in Chatbots&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Within our chatbots, this system allows us to explore how well of a system such as this would behave with our finetuned conversational language models such as our finetuned &lt;a href="https://huggingface.co/hitomi-team/convo-6B">Convo-6B&lt;/a> model.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://i.imgur.com/2daXOFw.png" alt="Example 2">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For our chatbots, the above message would appear like this:&lt;/p>
&lt;pre tabindex="0">&lt;code>haru: @Sakuya Izayoi hey
haru: [Image Attached: Image with the Touhou Project character Tenshi Hinanawi in it.]
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;p>This style of formatting helps our model know &lt;em>what&lt;/em> is in an image, even if the language model cannot actually see the image itself.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="limitations">Limitations&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>As mentioned above, this presents itself as a readily available solution for approximated vision with the tools that are presently available. There are numerous limitations with this technique as the only information extracted is very limited compared to what is in the image itself. After all, an image is worth a thousand words, but a more accurate saying for our use case would be &lt;code>an image is worth a thousand words that we can't cram into our Language Models or else our local GPUs would catch fire.&lt;/code> Or, less excitingly, a megabyte long error is produced.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>CLIP itself has a number of limitations as well, many of which are explained within their &lt;a href="https://openai.com/blog/clip/">own blog post&lt;/a> and &lt;a href="https://stanislavfort.github.io/blog/OpenAI_CLIP_stickers_and_adversarial_examples/">this one as well&lt;/a>. Essentially, CLIP is very prone to adversarial attacks where text within the image can influence the classification of an image according to CLIP.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Here is an example of that happening with our own chat bots where an image containing the phrase &lt;code>Alice&lt;/code> lead to the label &lt;code>Alice Margatroid&lt;/code> having a very high probability and ending up within the context sent to the Language Model:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://i.imgur.com/tRmDyDL.png" alt="Example 3">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;code>[Image Attached: Image with the Touhou Project character Alice Margatroid in it. This image depicts a amusement park. This is a sketch.&lt;/code>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="conclusion">Conclusion&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Using CLIP to classify an image with labels to approximate for chatbots is a great way to experiment on the limits of these systems without needing to do any heavy lifting ourselves. In order to mitigate against the limitations outlined above, we used several different techniques to prevent the appearance of such things while still allowing the conversation between human and machine to go smoothly.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For now, we will continue exploring this avenue of multimodal conversations with chatbots as it is something that could potentially open doors for future research in other areas outside of just computer science. We hope you enjoyed reading about our experience with Image Captioning with the help of CLIP.&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="links">Links&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://discord.gg/Sx6Spmsgx7">Discord Server&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://github.com/harubaru/eliza">The Code for the Chatbots&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://github.com/hitomi-team/sukima">Our Backend Software&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></content></item><item><title>It's Definitely Not Nitro!</title><link>https://hitomi-team.github.io/blog/dnn/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hitomi-team.github.io/blog/dnn/</guid><description>Announcing DNN (Definitely Not Nitro) TL;DR: The developers for Not Quite Nitro have a very misleading privacy policy that admits that their bot, Not Quite Nitro, stores sensitive information about users in the case of internal errors on their end without the user&amp;rsquo;s knowledge. We did not like their policy or practices, so we decided to make an open-source alternative.
What&amp;rsquo;s the Problem? We have a Discord server where user privacy is sacred.</description><content>&lt;h2 id="announcing-dnn-definitely-not-nitro">Announcing DNN (Definitely Not Nitro)&lt;/h2>
&lt;h2 id="tldr">TL;DR:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The developers for Not Quite Nitro have a very misleading privacy policy that admits that their bot, Not Quite Nitro, stores sensitive information about users in the case of internal errors on their end without the user&amp;rsquo;s knowledge. &lt;strong>We did not like their policy or practices, so we decided to make an open-source alternative.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://i.imgur.com/7oJLLst.png" alt="An example of the devs&amp;amp;rsquo; views on user privacy.">&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="whats-the-problem">What&amp;rsquo;s the Problem?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We have a &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/Sx6Spmsgx7">Discord server&lt;/a> where user privacy is sacred. We absolutely reject the notion that a user can implicitly consent to a service&amp;rsquo;s privacy policy by simply just using it even when they are not shown the service&amp;rsquo;s privacy policy. The data that is being collected without users&amp;rsquo; explicit consent is highly sensitive and highly personal as NQN records &lt;strong>User ID, User name &amp;amp; Discriminator, and the content of messages.&lt;/strong> Even though this is being done in the event of internal errors, this practice is &lt;strong>absolutely unacceptable&lt;/strong> to us.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="okay-now-whats-the-solution">Okay, now what&amp;rsquo;s the Solution?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We are developing a NQN alternative called &lt;strong>DNN (Definitely Not Nitro)&lt;/strong> that aims to be transparent, open source, and privacy respecting for everyone. The &lt;a href="https://hitomi-team.github.io/privacy">privacy policy&lt;/a> for our alternative basically states that absolutely no information about the user is being collected.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You can help us out with our development by joining our &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/Sx6Spmsgx7">Discord server&lt;/a> or contributing to the &lt;a href="https://github.com/hitomi-team/DNN">main repository!&lt;/a> We gladly welcome all sorts of help as we are short handed on the development efforts for DNN.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://discord.com/api/oauth2/authorize?client_id=972542466861465620&amp;amp;permissions=536871936&amp;amp;scope=bot">Bot Invite Link&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://discord.gg/Sx6Spmsgx7">Our Discord Server&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></content></item><item><title/><link>https://hitomi-team.github.io/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hitomi-team.github.io/projects/</guid><description>Come back soon! We are still writing this page.</description><content>&lt;p>Come back soon! We are still writing this page.&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://hitomi-team.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hitomi-team.github.io/about/</guid><description>Lorelei Labs is a group of volunteer developers who are focused on developing AI software that is sustainable, scalable, and most importantly, truly open for everyone.
We are most well known for our efforts in developing open source dialogue and story telling language models, but we do our own research and development towards the sustainable hosting of these gigantic AI models.</description><content>&lt;p>&lt;em>&lt;strong>Lorelei Labs&lt;/strong>&lt;/em> is a group of volunteer developers who are focused on developing AI software that is sustainable, scalable, and most importantly, truly open for everyone.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We are most well known for our efforts in developing open source dialogue and story telling language models, but we do our own research and development towards the sustainable hosting of these gigantic AI models.&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>Privacy</title><link>https://hitomi-team.github.io/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hitomi-team.github.io/privacy/</guid><description>Effective: May 7th, 2022
Contact: You can email us at anthony.mercurio@protonmail.com and our mailing address is 8607 West Mariposa Drive Phoenix, AZ 85037 United States.
Access to your Content. We will only access the content that you voluntarily make available to us in order to provide our Services to your account. Your content will not be viewed by any agent or member of Lorelei Labs without explicit consent from yourself. In order to perform our services, we may need to access, transform, and transmit your content between Lorelei Labs and yourself.</description><content>&lt;p>Effective: &lt;strong>May 7th, 2022&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Contact: You can email us at &lt;a href="mailto:anthony.mercurio@protonmail.com">anthony.mercurio@protonmail.com&lt;/a> and our mailing address is 8607 West Mariposa Drive Phoenix, AZ 85037 United States.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="access-to-your-content">Access to your Content.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We will only access the content that you voluntarily make available to us in order to provide our Services to your account. Your content will not be viewed by any agent or member of Lorelei Labs without explicit consent from yourself. In order to perform our services, we may need to access, transform, and transmit your content between Lorelei Labs and yourself.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="sharing-with-other-data-collectors">Sharing with other Data Collectors.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Unless processing payments or forced by law, we will &lt;strong>never&lt;/strong> share any of your data to Data Collectors or with any other third parties.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="logging">Logging.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We do not log the contents of requests made to our services without your explicit consent.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="retention">Retention.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We retain your data for as long as you have an active account with one of our services. If you close your account, we will &lt;strong>immediately&lt;/strong> and &lt;strong>irreversibly&lt;/strong> delete your data. At any time, you may request us to have your data voluntarily deleted.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="updates">Updates&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We will make updates to this Privacy Policy to reflect new changes in law, Lorelei Labs&amp;rsquo; organizational practices, new technologies, or for other purposes. If we do so, we will notify you within 30 days in advance in regards to any material changes to this policy.&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>Terms of Service</title><link>https://hitomi-team.github.io/terms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hitomi-team.github.io/terms/</guid><description>Effective: May 10th, 2022
Contact: You can email us at anthony.mercurio@protonmail.com and our mailing address is 8607 West Mariposa Drive Phoenix, AZ 85037 United States.
Term: The term of the agreement is until either party wishes to terminate this agreement through account deletion or termination by Lorelei Labs.
These terms of service apply to all of the services that Lorelei Labs provides and to agree to these terms, you also agree to our Privacy Policy.</description><content>&lt;p>Effective: &lt;strong>May 10th, 2022&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Contact: You can email us at &lt;a href="mailto:anthony.mercurio@protonmail.com">anthony.mercurio@protonmail.com&lt;/a> and our mailing address is 8607 West Mariposa Drive Phoenix, AZ 85037 United States.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Term: The term of the agreement is until either party wishes to terminate this agreement through account deletion or termination by Lorelei Labs.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>These terms of service apply to all of the services that Lorelei Labs provides and to agree to these terms, you also agree to our &lt;a href="https://hitomi-team.github.io/privacy">Privacy Policy&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="our-organization">Our Organization&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We provide services that allow general members of the public to utilize our software that can be provided either for free or through a subscription based order.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="data-privacy-protection">Data Privacy Protection&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We will comply with Data Protection Laws when regards to processing of user data as well as our &lt;a href="https://hitomi-team.github.io/privacy">Privacy Policy&lt;/a> which is incorporated into these terms.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="misuse">Misuse&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Through the use of our services, you must comply with the terms listed as well as all applicable laws and regulations. You must only use the services that we provide for authorized purposes. The restrictions for the use of our services are as follows:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Do not perform illegal activity:&lt;/strong> We do not allow the use of our services to commit or aid in illegal activity.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="termination">Termination&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>You reserve the right&lt;/strong> to discontinue your use of our services at any point for any reason.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>We reserve the right&lt;/strong> to terminate your account with or without advanced notice if:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>A breach of these terms is found.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A legal order or requirement forces us to do so.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="indemnity">Indemnity&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>You agree to indemnify Lorelei Labs and its members, officers, directors, and employees from and against all claims, damages, liabilities, and suits by third parties related to the access or use of our services, your violation of these terms, or the content you provide to our services.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="license-term">License Term&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Under acceptable compliance with the terms and applicable law, you may access and use the services that we provide and that you license from Lorelei Labs, Inc. Your license expires at the end of the term set forth in your seri&lt;/p></content></item></channel></rss>