<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lorelei Labs</title><link>http://example.org/</link><description>Recent content on Lorelei Labs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>It's Definitely Not Nitro!</title><link>http://example.org/blog/dnn/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/blog/dnn/</guid><description>Announcing DNN (Definitely Not Nitro) TL;DR: The developers for Not Quite Nitro have a very misleading privacy policy that admits to their bot, Not Quite Nitro, storing sensitive information about users in the case of internal errors on their end without their knowledge. We did not like their policy or practices, so we decided to make an open-source alternative.
What&amp;rsquo;s the Problem? We have a Discord server where user privacy is sacred.</description><content>&lt;h2 id="announcing-dnn-definitely-not-nitro">Announcing DNN (Definitely Not Nitro)&lt;/h2>
&lt;h2 id="tldr">TL;DR:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The developers for Not Quite Nitro have a very misleading privacy policy that admits to their bot, Not Quite Nitro, storing sensitive information about users in the case of internal errors on their end without their knowledge. &lt;strong>We did not like their policy or practices, so we decided to make an open-source alternative.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://i.imgur.com/7oJLLst.png" alt="An example of the devs&amp;amp;rsquo; views on user privacy.">&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="whats-the-problem">What&amp;rsquo;s the Problem?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We have a &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/Sx6Spmsgx7">Discord server&lt;/a> where user privacy is sacred. We absolutely reject the notion that a user can implicitly consent to a service&amp;rsquo;s privacy policy by simply just using it even when they are not shown the service&amp;rsquo;s privacy policy. The data that is being collected without users&amp;rsquo; explicit consent is highly sensitive and highly personal as NQN records &lt;strong>User ID, User name &amp;amp; Discriminator, and the content of messages.&lt;/strong> Even though this is being done in the event of internal errors, this practice is &lt;strong>absolutely unacceptable&lt;/strong> to us.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="okay-now-whats-the-solution">Okay, now what&amp;rsquo;s the Solution?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We are developing a NQN alternative called &lt;strong>DNN (Definitely Not Nitro)&lt;/strong> that aims to be transparent, open source, and privacy respecting for everyone. The &lt;a href="http://example.org/privacy">privacy policy&lt;/a> for our alternative basically states that absolutely no information about the user is being collected.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You can help us out with our development by joining our &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/Sx6Spmsgx7">Discord server&lt;/a> or contributing to the &lt;a href="https://github.com/hitomi-team/DNN">main repository!&lt;/a> We gladly welcome all sorts of help as we are short handed on the development efforts for DNN.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://discord.com/api/oauth2/authorize?client_id=972542466861465620&amp;amp;permissions=536871936&amp;amp;scope=bot">Bot Invite Link&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://discord.gg/Sx6Spmsgx7">Our Discord Server&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></content></item><item><title/><link>http://example.org/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/projects/</guid><description>Come back soon! We are still writing this page.</description><content>&lt;p>Come back soon! We are still writing this page.&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>http://example.org/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/about/</guid><description>Lorelei Labs is a group of volunteer developers who are focused on developing AI software that is sustainable, scalable, and most importantly, truly open for everyone.
We are most well known for our efforts in developing open source dialogue and story telling language models, but we do our own research and development towards the sustainable hosting of these gigantic AI models.</description><content>&lt;p>&lt;em>&lt;strong>Lorelei Labs&lt;/strong>&lt;/em> is a group of volunteer developers who are focused on developing AI software that is sustainable, scalable, and most importantly, truly open for everyone.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We are most well known for our efforts in developing open source dialogue and story telling language models, but we do our own research and development towards the sustainable hosting of these gigantic AI models.&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>Privacy</title><link>http://example.org/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/privacy/</guid><description>Effective: May 7th, 2022
Contact: You can email us at anthony.mercurio@protonmail.com and our mailing address is 8607 West Mariposa Drive Phoenix, AZ 85037 United States.
Access to your Content. We will only access the content that you voluntarily provide to us to provide our Services to your account. Your content will not be viewed by any agent or member of Lorelei Labs without explicit consent from yourself. In order to perform our services, we may need to access, transform, and transmit your content between Lorelei Labs and yourself.</description><content>&lt;p>Effective: &lt;strong>May 7th, 2022&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Contact: You can email us at &lt;a href="mailto:anthony.mercurio@protonmail.com">anthony.mercurio@protonmail.com&lt;/a> and our mailing address is 8607 West Mariposa Drive Phoenix, AZ 85037 United States.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="access-to-your-content">Access to your Content.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We will only access the content that you voluntarily provide to us to provide our Services to your account. Your content will not be viewed by any agent or member of Lorelei Labs without explicit consent from yourself. In order to perform our services, we may need to access, transform, and transmit your content between Lorelei Labs and yourself.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="sharing-with-other-data-collectors">Sharing with other Data Collectors.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Unless processing payments or forced by law, we will &lt;strong>never&lt;/strong> share any of your data to Data Collectors or with any other third parties.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="logging">Logging.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We do not log the contents of requests made to our services without your explicit consent.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="retention">Retention.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We retain your data for as long as you have an active account with one of our services. If you close your account, we will &lt;strong>immediately&lt;/strong> and &lt;strong>irreversibly&lt;/strong> delete your data. At any time, you may request us to have your data voluntarily deleted.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="updates">Updates&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We will make updates to this Privacy Policy to reflect new changes in law, Lorelei Labs&amp;rsquo; organizational practices, new technologies, or for other purposes. If we do so, we will notify you within 30 days in advance in regards to any material changes to this policy.&lt;/p></content></item></channel></rss>