<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Lorelei Labs</title><link>http://example.org/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Lorelei Labs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>It's Definitely Not Nitro!</title><link>http://example.org/blog/dnn/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/blog/dnn/</guid><description>Announcing DNN (Definitely Not Nitro) TL;DR: The developers for Not Quite Nitro have a very misleading privacy policy that admits to their bot, Not Quite Nitro, storing sensitive information about users in the case of internal errors on their end without their knowledge. We did not like their policy or practices, so we decided to make an open-source alternative.
What&amp;rsquo;s the Problem? We have a Discord server where user privacy is sacred.</description><content>&lt;h2 id="announcing-dnn-definitely-not-nitro">Announcing DNN (Definitely Not Nitro)&lt;/h2>
&lt;h2 id="tldr">TL;DR:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The developers for Not Quite Nitro have a very misleading privacy policy that admits to their bot, Not Quite Nitro, storing sensitive information about users in the case of internal errors on their end without their knowledge. &lt;strong>We did not like their policy or practices, so we decided to make an open-source alternative.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://i.imgur.com/7oJLLst.png" alt="An example of the devs&amp;amp;rsquo; views on user privacy.">&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="whats-the-problem">What&amp;rsquo;s the Problem?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We have a &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/Sx6Spmsgx7">Discord server&lt;/a> where user privacy is sacred. We absolutely reject the notion that a user can implicitly consent to a service&amp;rsquo;s privacy policy by simply just using it even when they are not shown the service&amp;rsquo;s privacy policy. The data that is being collected without users&amp;rsquo; explicit consent is highly sensitive and highly personal as NQN records &lt;strong>User ID, User name &amp;amp; Discriminator, and the content of messages.&lt;/strong> Even though this is being done in the event of internal errors, this practice is &lt;strong>absolutely unacceptable&lt;/strong> to us.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="okay-now-whats-the-solution">Okay, now what&amp;rsquo;s the Solution?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We are developing a NQN alternative called &lt;strong>DNN (Definitely Not Nitro)&lt;/strong> that aims to be transparent, open source, and privacy respecting for everyone. The &lt;a href="http://example.org/privacy">privacy policy&lt;/a> for our alternative basically states that absolutely no information about the user is being collected.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You can help us out with our development by joining our &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/Sx6Spmsgx7">Discord server&lt;/a> or contributing to the &lt;a href="https://github.com/hitomi-team/DNN">main repository!&lt;/a> We gladly welcome all sorts of help as we are short handed on the development efforts for DNN.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://discord.com/api/oauth2/authorize?client_id=972542466861465620&amp;amp;permissions=536871936&amp;amp;scope=bot">Bot Invite Link&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://discord.gg/Sx6Spmsgx7">Our Discord Server&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></content></item></channel></rss>